Society of Southwest Archivists records, Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Society of Southwest Archivists records
Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
1391
Society of Southwest Archivists
43 document boxes and 6 oversized boxes
The Society of Southwest Archivists records consist of manuscripts that chronicle the regional archival organization's history since the early 1970's. These records include correspondence, financial documents, legal documents, literary productions, and photographic materials that all recount the society's annual meetings, committee activities, and works pertaining to the general membership.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The Society of Southwest Archivists, founded in 1972, is the professional regional organization for archivists in Texas, New Mexico, Arizona, Oklahoma, Arkansas, and Louisiana. Organized to promote best archival practices, to educate members, and to foster interdisciplinary ties to historic preservation groups, the society has provided these services and more to hundreds of members throughout its history.
A group of interested people met to form the society in May 1972. These original founders drafted a constitution and elected officers. The first annual meeting, which fulfilled many of the initial goals of the organization, was held in 1973 in Norman, Oklahoma. After the second meeting in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, meetings were held in Texas for the next eleven years, but moved around the region more after 1986. Governed by a president and other officers comprising the Executive Board, the society gradually added various committees over time to select annual meeting sites, to design programs for the annual meeting, to produce a newsletter (The Southwestern Archivist), and to complete various other organizational functions. The society has also developed several awards that have been given to members and non-members through the years.
The Society of Southwest Archivists continues today to provide educational opportunities and promote best practices among its more than five hundred members.
Scope and Content
The Society of Southwest Archivists records include materials from the years prior to its organization in 1972 to 2017.
Series I. Annual Meetings contain correspondence, programs, photographs, registration materials, minutes, and other documents produced for or about the society’s annual meetings. The site moves each year, currently alternating between a Texas city and a non-Texas city.
Series II. Committee Documents, the largest series in the collection, consists of minutes, correspondence, notes, reports, and other materials pertaining to the society’s officers and committees. These committees highlight the various functions of the organization.
Series III. General Membership, as its name suggests, houses materials pertaining to the society’s membership. Prominent materials include membership directories, copies of the society’s newsletter The Southwestern Archivist, essays detailing brief historical accounts of the society, as well as other materials.
This collection contains flash drives, audio cassettes, compact discs, and floppy disks that were not able to be read at the time this finding aid was created. Once a machine is located that can read these materials, all documents should be printed and placed within the collection.
Researchers looking for information on specific annual meetings should consult the appropriate folders in the annual meeting series as well as those in the local arrangements committee subseries of the committee series.
Arrangement
Prior to this finding aid, the collection had been partially arranged and inventoried according to creator and occasionally by year. Extensive reorganization to make the collection more accessible to the researcher was necessary, including filing manuscripts by committee rather than person. The original order for much of the annual meeting series was maintained.
Currently, the Society of Southwest Archivists records are arranged in three series: I. Annual Meeting Materials, II. Committee Documents, and III. General Membership. Series I. is further divided into subseries based on the specific annual meeting, while Series II. is arranged according to committee or office.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1391. Acquired 1976-04-29
Related Resources
Related references
Schultz, Charles R. “Society of Southwest Archivists: The First Two Decades.” Lubbock, Texas, 1992.
“Society of Southwest Archivists.” Accessed 2012 March 16.
“Two Decades of Fun, Frivolity, and Professionalism: The SSA Experience.” Norman, Oklahoma, 1992.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Society of Southwest Archivists -- History.; Society of Southwest Archivists.
Subjects
Archives -- Southwestern States.; Archivists -- Societies, etc.
Genres
Correspondence.; Directories.; Essays.; Financial records.; Financial statements.; Handbooks and manuals.; Membership lists.; Minutes (Records); Newsletters.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Programs.
- Annual Meeting Materials, 1972-2015, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains correspondence, programs, minutes, registration forms, notes, and other materials pertaining to the annual meetings held by the Society of Southwest Archivists. The amount of material varies by year and relative proximity to Texas and The Texas Collection, so there are some notable gaps in the series. The materials, overall, are in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  35 mm negative film (color); Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Flash memory devices; Photographic print
  - 1st Annual Meeting, 1972-1973; 1
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Ballot Materials and Opinionnaires, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Literary: General, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Program, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Rosters, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Audio Cassette, 1973 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Archival Box from 1st Annual Meeting (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Archival Box from 1st Annual Meeting (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 2nd Annual Meeting, 1974; 2
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Literary: General, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 3rd Annual Meeting, 1974-1975, undated; 3
    - Correspondence, 1974 June-July (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1974 August-December (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1975 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1975 February-March 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1975 March 11-13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1975 March 18-31 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1975 April (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1975 May (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1975 June-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Financial, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Resolutions, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Literary: General, 1975, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Program, 1975 May 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 4th Annual Meeting, 1975-1976, undated; 4
    - Correspondence, 1975 May-July (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1975 August-October (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1975 November (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1975 December-1976 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January 16-February (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1976 March 5-25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1976 March 26-30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1976 March 31-April 12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1976 April 14-May 11 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1976 May 12-19 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1976 May 20-June (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Financial: General, 1976 April-May 5 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Financial: General, 1976 May 7-September (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Financial: General, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Legal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Agendas, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Brochures, circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Literary: General, 1975-1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Registration Lists (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Registration Lists (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Minutes: Business Session, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Notes (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Notes (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Photographic, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 5th Annual Meeting, 1976-1977; 5
    - Correspondence, 1976 June-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1977 January-March (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1977 April-October (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Literary: General, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1977 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Literary: People Attending, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Programs, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 6th Annual Meeting, 1977-1978; 6
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 January (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1978 February (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1978 March-May 8 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1978 May 9-31 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Literary: General, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Program, 1978 May 3-5 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 7th Annual Meeting, 1978-1979; 7
    - Correspondence, 1978 September-November (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1978 December-1979 January (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1979 February-May (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Literary: General, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Notes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 8th Annual Meeting, 1977-1980; 8
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1979 October 24-November (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1979 December-1980 January (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1980 February-March (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1980 April-May 13 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1980 May 14-June (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Financial, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Business Session (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Business Session (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Literary: General, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Hotel, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Literary: People Attending, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Programs, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 9th Annual Meeting, 1981; 9
    - Literary: Minutes, 1981 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Program and Roster, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Audio Cassette, 1981 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 10th Annual Meeting, 1982; 10
    - Literary: Program, 1982 May 12-14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 11th Annual Meeting, 1983; 11
    - Literary: Address, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Literary: General, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1983 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 12th Annual Meeting, 1983-1984, undated; 12
    - Correspondence, 1983 March-June (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1983 September-1984 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1984 February 17-March (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1984 May-September, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Financial, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Proceedings (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Proceedings (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Proceedings (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Proceedings and Program, 1984 May (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 13th Annual Meeting, 1985; 13
    - Literary: General, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1985 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Proceedings (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Proceedings (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Proceedings (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Program, 1985 May 8-10 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 14th Annual Meeting, 1986; 14
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Literary: General, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1986 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Program, 1986 May 21-23 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 15th Annual Meeting, 1986-1988; 15
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 January (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1987 February (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1987 April-1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Financial, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Literary: General, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1987 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Programs, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Registration Materials, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 16th Annual Meeting, 1986-1988, undated; 16
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 July (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1987 October-1988 January (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1988 February-April (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1988 May 2-25 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1988 May 26-August, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Financial, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Board Session, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Notes, circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Program (1 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Program (2 of 2), circa 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Reports, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Speech: Bryan (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Speech: Bryan (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Speech: Bryan (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Speeches: Bryan, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Speeches: Garrett, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Speeches: McLean, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Speeches: Neal (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Speeches: Neal (2 of 4), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Speeches: Neal (3 of 4), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Speeches: Neal (4 of 4), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Speeches: Wilson (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Speeches: Wilson (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Speeches: Wilson (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Audio Cassette, 1988 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Audio Cassette: Panel: "Can Archivists Be Sued-And If So, For What?", 1988 May 19 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 17th Annual Meeting, 1989; 17
    - Literary: Business Session, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Literary: General, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1989 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Program, 1989 May 18-20 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 18th Annual Meeting, 1988-1990, undated; 18
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 January (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1990 February-March (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1990 April-August (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Financial, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Literary: General, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Notes, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 2), 1989-1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 2), 1989-1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Programs, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Literary: Registration, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Literary: Resolutions, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 19th Annual Meeting, 1990-1991, undated; 19
    - Correspondence, 1990 February-September (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1990 November-1991 February (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March-June (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Financial, circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Legal, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Notes (1 of 2), circa 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Notes (2 of 2), circa 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 3), circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 3), circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (3 of 3), circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Poster Materials, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Program (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Program (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Registration, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Speeches, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Poster, 1991 (Box [1063] OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 20th Annual Meeting, 1989-1992, undated; 20
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1990 June 14-November (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1990 December-1991 May (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1991 June-December (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1992 February-March (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1992 April-June (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Legal, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Literary: General, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Notes, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Presentation Materials: "JFK in Texas: Kennedy Assassination Materials in Texas", 1992 June 6-8 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Program, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Registration Packet, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 21st Annual Meeting, 1992-1993; 21
    - Correspondence, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Financial, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Literary: General, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Registration Packet, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 22nd Annual Meeting, 1993-1994, undated; 22
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994 February (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994 February (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994 March-April (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994 March-April (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1994 May 3-6 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1994 May 8-23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1994 June-August, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Financial, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Blank Forms, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Notes, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Programs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Registration, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Photographic, circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 23rd Annual Meeting, 1995, undated; 23
    - Correspondence, 1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Contracts, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Literary: General, circa 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Program, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Registration, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 24th Annual Meeting, 1996; 24
    - Literary: General, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 25th Annual Meeting, 1995-1997, undated; 25
    - Correspondence, 1995 July-1996 May (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1996 July-August (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1996 September-October (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1996 November-December (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1996 November-December (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1997 January-February (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1997 March-May (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1997 June 4-6 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1997 June 9-August, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Financial, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Legal, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Literary: General (1 of 4), circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Literary: General (2 of 4), circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Literary: General (3 of 4), circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Literary: General (4 of 4), circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Programs, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Registration, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 26th Annual Meeting, 1997-1998, undated; 26
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Literary: General, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1998 May 30 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Literary: Program, 1998 May 28-30 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Registration, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Photographs (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Negatives (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Negatives (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 27th Annual Meeting, 1998-1999, undated; 27
    - Correspondence, 1998 July-September (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1998 October 13-26 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1998 October 26-November (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1998 December-1999 April (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1999 May-June 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1999 June 2-7 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1999 June 2-7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1999 June 8-August (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Business Session, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Literary: General, circa 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: General (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: General (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: General (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)